♪When darkness gathers, flowing like a river♪
♪عندما يتجمع الظلام، يجري مثل النهر♪
♪We stand apart at distant ends♪
♪نقف متباعدين عند النهايات البعيدة♪
♪Bound by fate, we fight with no way back♪
♪مقيدون بالقدر، نقاتل بلا عودة♪
♪Once we act, no regrets remain♪
♪حالما نتحرك، لا يبقى ندم♪
♪Defying the looming foreboding♪
♪نتحدى النذر المشؤومة♪
♪Breaking free from tangled strands♪
♪ننطلق من الخيوط المتشابكة♪
♪Lost in the dark, with bullets cold♪
♪تائهون في الظلام، برصاص بارد♪
♪Till all fades away like smoke♪
♪حتى يتبدد كل شيء مثل الدخان♪
=Hide Games=
=ألعاب الاختباء=
=Episode 12=
=الحلقة 12=
(Wu) Master, where are you?
(وو) أستاذ، أين أنت؟
I found a clue in 405.
وجدت دليلاً في الغرفة 405.
Eight tonight at the usual place.
الثامنة الليلة في المكان المعتاد.
This poor soul
هذه الروح المسكينة
was supposed to meet you tonight at eight.
كان من المفترض أن تلتقي بك الليلة في الثامنة.
But he can't wait any longer.
لكنه لا يستطيع الانتظار أكثر.
Only you can save him now.
أنت الوحيد الذي يمكنه إنقاذه الآن.
Han Xu.
هان شو.
Over here.
هنا.
Don't move.
لا تتحرك.
Master.
أستاذ.
Think.
فكر.
Tell me who he is.
أخبرني من هو.
Master.
أستاذ.
Who is he?
من هو؟
- Master. - Who is he?
- أستاذ. - من هو؟
Tell me who he is.
أخبرني من هو.
Who is he?
من هو؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Think. Who is he?
فكر. من هو؟
Tell me who he is.
أخبرني من هو.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Seems you really like this pendant.
يبدو أنكِ تحبين هذا المعلقة حقًا.
My dad gave it to me.
والدي أهداني إياها.
I've always treated it as my amulet.
لطالما اعتبرتها تعويذتي.
Now, I want you to have it.
الآن، أريدك أن تحتفظي بها.
When we meet again,
عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى،
you can give it back to me.
يمكنكِ إعادتها لي.
Nuo, go back to your room.
نو، عودي إلى غرفتك.
Mom, I want to let...
أمي، أريد أن...
Be good.
كوني مطيعة.
Alright.
حسنًا.
Sorry about that.
آسفة على ذلك.
She really misses her dad.
إنها تفتقد والدها حقًا.
Where is this place?
أين هذا المكان؟
How did I end up here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
This is my old house.
هذا منزلي القديم.
Don't worry; it's safe here.
لا تقلق؛ المكان آمن هنا.
What happened to you?
ماذا حدث لك؟
Did you remember anything?
هل تذكرت أي شيء؟
Can I trust you?
هل يمكنني الوثوق بك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
You have to trust me.
عليك أن تثق بي.
After all you've been through...
بعد كل ما مررت به...
Nothing came back to you?
لم يعد إليك أي ذكرى؟
Nothing at all.
لا شيء على الإطلاق.
I just felt
شعرت فقط
a bit disappointed
ببعض خيبة الأمل
and sad.
والحزن.
Nothing else.
لا شيء آخر.
I hope everything goes well
آمل أن يسير كل شيء على ما يرام
and Chen can make it.
وأن يتمكن تشين من النجاح.
If you want to succeed,
إذا كنت تريد النجاح،
don't rush the plan too much.
لا تستعجل الخطة كثيرًا.
Now, it's full of holes.
الآن، أصبحت مليئة بالثغرات.
Don't think I don't know
لا تظن أنني لا أعرف
the things you did in secret.
الأشياء التي فعلتها سرًا.
The one who is ruining the plan
الشخص الذي يدمر الخطة
is you.
هو أنت.
If you'd like,
إذا كنت ترغب،
I can try hypnosis again.
يمكنني تجربة التنويم المغناطيسي مرة أخرى.
Let's give it a shot.
لنجربها.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Mom.
أمي.
I'll wash my face and get ready.
سأغسل وجهي وأستعد.
Director.
أيها المخرج.
You said it.
أنت من قال ذلك.
This is my case,
هذه قضيتي،
and I'll take charge of everything.
وسأتولى كل شيء.
Right here.
هنا بالضبط.
Send a few more people downstairs.
أرسل المزيد من الأشخاص إلى الطابق السفلي.
Let's just wait and see.
لننتظر ونرى.
He doesn't trust me anymore.
لم يعد يثق بي.
Got it.
فهمت.
Chief Han.
الرئيس هان.
This call came later than I expected.
هذه المكالمة جاءت متأخرة عما توقعت.
You seem to know me pretty well.
يبدو أنك تعرفني جيدًا.
Of course, better than you think.
بالطبع، أكثر مما تظن.
How else would I prepare such a thoughtful gift?
كيف كنت سأعد هدية مدروسة كهذه؟
I told you
أخبرتك
I'd get a return gift for you.
أنني سأحضر لك هدية مقابلة.
I'm going to kill you.
سأقتلك.
Want to kill me?
تريد قتلي؟
Figure out who I am first.
اكتشف من أكون أولاً.
I will find out.
سأكتشف ذلك.
How many days have we been here?
كم يومًا كنا هنا؟
What are we waiting for?
ما الذي ننتظره؟
Did we mess something up at work?
هل أفسدنا شيئًا في العمل؟
Is that why they sent us here?
هل هذا هو سبب إرسالنا إلى هنا؟
- Look at that. - Stop whining.
- انظر إلى ذلك. - توقف عن التذمر.
Let's finish this and go.
لننهِ هذا ونذهب.
We can grab drinks after.
يمكننا تناول المشروبات لاحقًا.
Let's leave now.
لنغادر الآن.
No way.
مستحيل.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Hey man, did this phone get wet?
يا رجل، هل تبلل هذا الهاتف؟
Luckily, it's this model.
لحسن الحظ، إنه هذا الموديل.
Or I wouldn't have taken it.
وإلا لما أخذته.
Name your price.
سمّ سعرك.
Give me however much you want.
أعطني المبلغ الذي تريده.
There's an audio recording inside.
يوجد تسجيل صوتي بداخله.
Save it to this USB drive.
احفظه على محرك USB هذا.
Take the fee from that.
خذ الأجر من ذلك.
Got it.
فهمت.
(Import Sound)
(استيراد الصوت)
Of course,
بالطبع،
better than you think.
أفضل مما تظن.
How else would I prepare
كيف كنت سأعد
such a thoughtful gift?
هدية مدروسة كهذه؟
(Sound Synthesis)
(تركيب الصوت)
Want to kill me?
تريد قتلي؟
Chief Han.
الرئيس هان.
Figure out who I am first.
اكتشف من أكون أولاً.
(Analysis Successful) Want to kill me?
(التحليل ناجح) تريد قتلي؟
Figure out who I am first.
اكتشف من أكون أولاً.
Want a combat?
تريد قتالاً؟
Wait until you're healed.
انتظر حتى تتعافى.
No problem, that's what friends do.
لا مشكلة، هذا ما يفعله الأصدقاء.
Please.
من فضلك.
Take care of my sister for me.
اعتني بأختي من أجلي.
Can you do that?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
If you hadn't come to me,
لو لم تأتِ إليّ،
you'd never spot the trick.
لن تكتشف الخدعة أبدًا.
She's really naive.
إنها ساذجة حقًا.
I'm afraid she'll get scammed.
أخشى أن يتم خداعها.
Someone made me say that.
أجبرني أحدهم على قول ذلك.
Hey, I want to check out.
مرحبًا، أريد تسجيل الخروج.
Single room.
غرفة فردية.
ID, please.
الهوية، من فضلك.
I forgot to bring it.
نسيت إحضارها.
100 for an 85-room.
100 للغرفة 85.
Second floor.
الطابق الثاني.
The one at the end of the hall.
الغرفة في نهاية الممر.
(Feels like Home)
(أشعر وكأنني في المنزل)
(Xiao Ran, An Shaocong, Wang Jian, Chen Yasin, Zhang Ahua, Chief Ma)
(شياو ران، أن شاوكونغ، وانغ جيان، تشن ياسين، تشانغ آهوا، الرئيس ما)
It was from a temporary number.
كان من رقم مؤقت.
He said
قال
his name was Han Xu.
اسمه هان شو.
(Was it me? The killer?)
(هل كنت أنا؟ القاتل؟)
I just saw the whole crime happen.
لقد رأيت الجريمة بأكملها تحدث.
Like I was right there in it.
وكأنني كنت هناك بالضبط.
(Chen Yasin)
(تشن ياسين)
From what I see,
من وجهة نظري،
you don't have a split personality.
ليس لديك انفصام في الشخصية.
(Watch out)
(انتبه)
(Director Zhou) If you choose wrong,
(المخرج تشو) إذا اخترت خطأ،
there's no turning back.
لا عودة بعدها.
(Wang Jian, police, plot) I won't let you get away again.
(وانغ جيان، الشرطة، المؤامرة) لن أدعك تهرب مرة أخرى.
(Police, plot)
(الشرطة، المؤامرة)
I'll look into everything.
سأتحقق من كل شيء.
(Wu, trusted friend) Only we know this dialect.
(وو، الصديق الموثوق) نحن الوحيدون الذين نعرف هذه اللهجة.
(An Shaocong) Reliable.
(أن شاوكونغ) موثوق.
(Chen Yasin) Don't give up.
(تشن ياسين) لا تستسلم.
(Reliable, Zhang Ahua)
(موثوق، تشانغ آهوا)
(Xiao Ran)
(شياو ران)
(Memories)
(ذكريات)
(Was it me? The killer?)
(هل كنت أنا؟ القاتل؟)
(Chief Ma, Director Zhou)
(الرئيس ما، المخرج تشو)
(Director Zhou)
(المخرج تشو)
(Wu)
(وو)
(Odd)
(غريب)
(Ma)
(ما)
(Zhou)
(تشو)
(Ahua)
(آهوا)
(An)
(أن)
(Ran)
(ران)
(Chen)
(تشن)
(Wang)
(وانغ)
(Me)
(أنا)
(Memories coming back)
(عودة الذكريات)
(The student could be fake)
(قد يكون الطالب مزيفًا)
How did your mom teach you?
كيف علمتك أمك؟
I asked for cigarettes, yet you brought water.
طلبت سجائر، لكنك أحضرت ماء.
How did you mix up water and cigarettes?
كيف خلطت بين الماء والسجائر؟
You always speak dialect.
أنت تتحدث باللهجة دائمًا.
I can't understand you.
لا أستطيع فهمك.
No dialect next time.
لا لهجة في المرة القادمة.
Get me a glass of water.
احضر لي كوب ماء.
Water.
ماء.
It's been ages since I spoke dialect.
مرت سنين منذ أن تحدثت باللهجة.
I can barely catch the words.
بالكاد أستطيع فهم الكلمات.
(Wu)
(وو)
Officer 67234 reporting in.
الضابط 67234 يقدم تقريره.
From now on, you'll be my master.
من الآن فصاعدًا، ستكون معلمي.
There's a bit of history between us.
هناك القليل من التاريخ بيننا.
So, please look out for me.
لذا، أرجو أن ترعاني.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I don't think I've seen you before.
لا أعتقد أنني رأيتك من قبل.
You don't know?
ألا تعرف؟
I'm your junior.
أنا تلميذك.
In the whole South District,
في المنطقة الجنوبية بأكملها،
only we share a hometown.
نحن الوحيدون الذين نتشارك مسقط الرأس.
Back home, you're a big deal.
في بلدتنا، أنت شخص مهم.
Did you know that?
هل كنت تعلم ذلك؟
Master,
معلمي،
have some water.
تناول بعض الماء.
how about a cigarette?
ماذا عن سيجارة؟
It's been ages since I heard our accent.
مرت سنين منذ أن سمعت لهجتنا.
You speak it really well.
أنت تتحدثها بطلاقة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
I grew up there for over 20 years.
لقد نشأت هناك لأكثر من 20 عامًا.
It's in my bones.
إنها في دمي.
No way I got this wrong.
من المستحيل أن أخطئ في هذا.
(Wu)
(وو)
It's been ages since I spoke dialect.
مرت سنين منذ أن تحدثت باللهجة.
I can barely catch the words.
بالكاد أستطيع فهم الكلمات.
Officer 67234 reporting in.
الضابط 67234 يقدم تقريره.
From now on, you'll be my master.
من الآن فصاعدًا، ستكون معلمي.
♪Waiting for the fragrance of flowers♪
♪في انتظار عطر الأزهار♪
♪To cross over the high wall♪
♪ليعبر الجدار العالي♪
♪Waiting for the shore♪
♪في انتظار الشاطئ♪
♪To forget the storm♪
♪لينسى العاصفة♪
♪Just like this♪
♪هكذا تمامًا♪
♪Wasting a few inches♪
♪أهدر بضع بوصات♪
♪Of daylight♪
♪من ضوء النهار♪
♪Half for the memories♪
♪نصفها للذكريات♪
♪Half for the dreams♪
♪ونصفها للأحلام♪
♪Oh, little boat♪
♪أيها القارب الصغير♪
♪Where are you going♪
♪إلى أين تذهب♪
♪No need to answer that♪
♪لا حاجة للإجابة♪
♪Just let me♪
♪دعني فقط♪
♪Watch you drift away♪
♪أراقبك تنجرف بعيدًا♪
♪Into the sunset glow♪
♪نور غروب الشمس♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪لا تخف♪
♪This world♪
♪هذا العالم♪
♪Is vast as it may be♪
♪واسع كما قد يبدو♪
♪But there's always♪
♪لكن هناك دائمًا♪
♪Someone who cares♪
♪من يهتم لأمرك♪
♪Shining like a lighthouse♪
♪يضيء كمنارة♪